Similar to the old discussion, this notation gives the title lower bound of that given algorithm.
And would it present it by f of an omega g of an so omega notation is giving the lower bound and the
oh notation, giving the upper bound a fine and creating more a function?
That means at larger values of and the tighter, lower bound of g of F of and G of and for example.
If we consider F of an.
Equal one hundred and square plus then and plus fifty.
If we need to consider the oh of an.
Oh, of and for this function is the highest and highest value is.
And square and the omega notation for this.
Sort of and square.
And it is of oh, and square, OK, Omega.
And the square, because it is the tighter, lower bound so that omega annotation can be defined as
omega notation of g of an equal to f of and there exists positive constancy and and and zero.
For that function, where zero between and the function of JioTV and between zero and F of fat, so
they're zero equal less than or equal g of ten times to less than half of.
Our objective is to give the largest rate of growth of JioTV and which is less than or equal to that
given and good at the rate of growth.
For example, if we have here a lower give, a lower bound of like f of and square OK, give.
Lower bound.
Of.
F of an equal to five and the square, OK, the upper bound here is and the square.
OK.
The lower power there exists, see?
And square and n0 such that zero less than or equal seat times and the square less than five and square.
So there exists and zero and sees such sexy times and square less than five and square less than half
of.
And this is the function that we.
And this is the formula that we are working to find the lower back.
OK.
See, and the square less than.
Five and square, so see equal to five and zero, equal to one.
So the thetan asserted that omega notation of this function is and squared.
This is the same for some examples.
It is the same as the old notation, but it's very simple.
We can consider this as a function and we are going to work with in many ways.